See? It's hot
All the dogs go to sleep under the car.
It's cooler under the car.
They've made the right choice!
Let me touch your dog head, ah.
Um! It's very comfortable here.
Is that great?
Other people need to pay for a massage.
But my massage is, is free.
Give you a massage. It's free.
It enjoys a lot.
The dogs are now that big. Especially this dog. It is the biggest
and fat.
Wa, Blacky,
its string is a little bit tight.
Let me cut it away.
Otherwise, it is squeezing her neck.
Wa! It's too tight. My brother did that.
Let me cut it away later.
See? Her hair, is shiny black, under my care.
When she came back from my brother's home
although the hair was still back, but it was not that smooth.
Wa! See? Now is so smooth.
Blacky, do you like being here? Do you like my place or brother's place? Ah?
Whose place do you like?
Come here!
See her teeth?
She is laughing, see? Grinning merrily. Oh!
Look at yourself! You are so dirty!
It's because I don't wash you.
I am too busy, otherwise I can give you a bathe.
Why don't you jump into the river and wash yourself?
She is very big now.
She is now at least...
almost...
Let me see how heavy you are!
Let me weigh you.
Aiya!
Aiyo!
Did I hurt you?
Okay! I'll leave you alone.
More than 10kg
I want to check your teeth! Come on!
You see? See? Her teeth
Her teeth are very white, even whiter than mine.
She never brushes her teeth, but she has whiter teeth than I do. How can it be?
I can't understand the rule.
Is it because she is eats everyday, eating
I mean crushing bones can whiten the teeth?
Huh! I will tie you up! You are so naughty!
Be a good dog! Lie down!
Come here! Let me get rid of the string.
Trust me! I just want to get rid of the string.
Wa! Why is the string so...
See? You feel much better now, don't you?
Don't you?
Brother made it.... he is too bad.
She likes me very much. See? She is always licking me.
See? This is Mr. Cameraman's most favourite dog.
This, this dog.
Eh? What is it? Here.
A scar. He was wounded.
Do you like Mr. Cameraman? Ah?
Do you like him? Marry him if you like? Go!
It's too hot. They are all lying here. Cool!
Cool! Cool!
Blacky is now much fatter, now.
Don't bite me! You are so big now. You can't bite me!
I'll show you the consequence if you bite me. Don't say that I have not warned you.
You go to play over there first. Don't stay here!
Why are you coming? I don't want you!
See?
She just likes...why? None of your business!
Have a look at this dog.
See?
She is good at...
I am sure she is...
When I... then she is...
Lick me, lick me! Don't lick her.
Go away, go away! This Blacky, go away!
I say go away! I don't want you!
This dog is, chubby and fat.
This dog, big dog.
You have not taken a shower for a long time. See? You are so dirty.
Next time I will wash her when I can take some time.
Do you get it? I will wash you. Do you want?
Do you?
Next time I will wash her when I can take some time.
Wa! There is a lot of flesh, on this side.
Very fat!
Wa! Her fangs!
Let me see your teeth! Why are your teeth, dog's teeth always so white?
They never brush the teeth.
Um! See her claw?
Hand hand!
This is "hand hand", got it?
Next time when I,
when I say "hand hand", I' give you a bone if you give me your hand.
otherwise, you'll have only leaves.
You can give me this hand too, got it?
See? Here is a wound. She must have had a fight.
The wound is minor, no worries.
See? "Gong Xi Fa Cai" (Wish you a good fortune)
Oh!
This dog is big. The ears are big.
Be a good dog! Got it?
Don't bite people!
Don't bite my chicks!
If you do, I will, sell you!
Are you scared? I will sell you!